#### Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/ion-catalin-rabuga-9415b945 (LinkedIn)

#### Top Skills

Healthcare

Medical Education

Clinical Research

# **ION-CATALIN RABUGA**

Medic Specialist

Horezu, Vâlcea, Romania

# Summary

Experienced Doctor with a demonstrated history of working in the medical practice industry. Skilled in Clinical Research, Medical Education, Medicine, Public Speaking, and Research. Strong healthcare services professional with a medic specialist mf focused in medicina from Universitatea de Medicină și Farmacie din Craiova.

## Experience

UPU HOREZU UPU-January 2014 - Present (9 years 7 months) HOREZU VALCEA

CMI Dr.RABUGA ION CATALIN DOCTOR 2000 - Present (23 years)

centrul urgenta baile govora Medical Specialist January 2009 - December 2013 (5 years) baile govora

centrul socio-medical obrocesti Medical Specialist January 2006 - December 2008 (3 years) obrocesti

### Education

Universitatea de Medicină și Farmacie din Târgu-Mureș MEDIC · (1992 - 1998)

Universitatea de Medicină și Farmacie din Craiova

medic specialist mf, medicina · (2008 - 2013)

UNIVERSITATEA DE MEDICINA SIBIU

COMPETENTA ULTRASONOGRAFIE GENERALA · (2009 - 2011)